[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "What does it make you feel like when on a Harley?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "It's total freedom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Arianna, knowing you, I would imagine you're a bit fed one only being 31 on this list, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "CD", "RB", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I think it's a great list.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "But quietly you're thinking, hang original I should be at least in the 20s here, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Would it matter what you're now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "If you're second to Warren Buffett, you're really annoyed, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "What has gone wrong with America Incorporated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, what's happened is that for many, many years now, we've seen the life of the middle class being much more precarious.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "And what is actually ironic is that the big ideas are now small ideas at the community level.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "What do you think about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "At least.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Do you think she has in her to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "To create the jobs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Do you know Steve jobs personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "As you, someone who has laid this incredible business yourself, the \"Huffington Post\" -- could you ever imagine that moment of giving up the reins to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, I can imagine the moment is much harder to contemplate that moment because of premature reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Oh, when did you say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "I just did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "You don't take any nonsense, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Not from dogs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["International Living"]}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What was your first impression?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "You know, I came to American when I was 16 as part of a program called The Experiment in International Living.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bernard Levin"]}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "What was he thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Bernard Levin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", "JJR", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Do you wish that he had wanted to get married and had children and stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, I was -- not anymore, because my whole life would have been entirely different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "So, what's going on there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, we are actually doing amazing things on the content side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Over 1,300.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Do you feel uneasy actually paying people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I'm loving it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Do you ever look in the mirror, Arianna, and think I haven't done badly for a young lady from Greece?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I haven't look in the mirror and think, I'm always in the end going to be a Greek peasant girl at heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arianna", "Greece"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Were you, even though you knew it would be provocative, taken aback by the scale of protests that came your way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Absolutely, and by the national attention.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Knowing what you know now, would you have played things differently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Was there ever a moment in all that when you looked in the mirror and thought, Scott, I could be the shortest term governor in the history of Wisconsin here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "You know, throughout the mix of it, I didn't ever think about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott"], "LOCATION": ["Wisconsin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "What is your message to them to allay that concern?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, my message would be more for the workers of our state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "When you turn up and you see this kind of thing, what goes through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "In this case, it was one of the extremes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Have you had death threats?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Oh, absolutely, stacks of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Any of them taken seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "We took them all seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Have you had them actually turn up at any of the houses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Anyone making proper threats?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "No, in those cases most of the threats were without names or numbers of that attached.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Has it just become too visceral, too personal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Too unsavory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I think it has.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Where do you think the clever money should be going now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "As you can imagine, I have a bias toward governors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last ten years"]}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "NN", ":", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Yes, except even part -- out of curiosity, I looked over the last ten years, the oil industry, as an example, is a smaller percentage of the economy than it was a decade ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Tax cuts even?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "So the debate becomes, how do you get America in business terms confident again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "If I held a metaphorical gun to your head and said, who should be top dog and who's the running mate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "You know, right now, it's just too early.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Quite a little boy racer, aren't you, governor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I love them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "What were your thoughts when you heard her say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Well, I was amazed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "What does it make you feel like when you're on a Harley?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Total freedom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]